<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>!! ReactionAPI</name>
    <directory>!! reactionapi</directory>
    <id>3096181411</id>
    <description>[h1]ReactionAPI[/h1]

An [b]API[/b] that greatly eases the creation of 'Reaction to Quality Items' Mods.

This mod represents the brain of those mods, the part that scans the room for items and finds the best quality.
As such if the mod is installed alone it will only impact performance, without adding any visual flair.

This API aims to improve the previously utilized scanning methodology by:

[list]
    [*] Preventing the execution of Code in rooms where there are no Item Pedestals.
	[*] Making sure that regardless of how many 'Reaction' Mods have been enabled, the scanning process is only executed once.
	[*] Provides better interaction with Glitched Items and Cycling Pedestals ([spoiler]Glitched Crown, T.Isaac Effect[/spoiler]).
	[*] Provides the tools for mod creators to easily implement Compatibility patches for effects that modify Item mechanics.
	[*] Allows users to customize the Quality of each item (including modded ones), freeing the developers from having to create a settings menu, and the users from having to manually synchronize their preferences across multiple mods (This is only possible whilst using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2681875787]Mod Config Menu[/url]).
[/list]

Additionally the mod keeps track of all the Item Pedestals present within the current room, giving easy access to information such as: blind status of a pedestal, the items present within a Cycling Pedestal and their cycle order.

Visit the [url=https://github.com/Guantol-Lemat/Isaac.ReactionAPI]Github repository[/url] for more info on how to implement the API within your mod.

This mod also has built-in compatibility with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2724039000]Cursed Collection[/url] treating Items during Curse of the Blight as Blind items.</description>
    <version>1.1</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Pickups"/>
</metadata>
